(Sheldon:)Raj, now, I'm sorry
you're suffering.
(Sheldon:)When Amy and I were
broken up, I also suffered.
(Sheldon:)And this may
sound surprising,
(Sheldon:)but I'm grateful for
having gone through it.
(Bernadette:)Really?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)I believe our relationship
now is stronger than ever.
(Amy:)So do I.
When-when we were apart,
(Sheldon:)I learned how important
you are to me.
(Sheldon:)And I realize
(Sheldon:)that when two people are
in love, sometimes they...
BOTH:
Happy Valentine's Day!
(whooping)
We are young and fun!
(horn honking)
(Sheldon:)I stand corrected.
Fun.
(Sheldon:)Congratulations on a
successful live show.
(Amy:)And a lovely
Valentine's Day.
(Penny:)Cleaning up
is not young and fun.
(Leonard:)It can be.
Confetti fight!
(Leonard:)Maybe you should take a break.
(Leonard:)I got this.
(Sheldon:)Did you know the singular
of confetti is "confetto"?
(Amy:)Interesting, and when
would you use the singular?
(Sheldon:)I'm glad you asked.
(Sheldon:)Amy, you have a
confetto in your nose.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no, no. Other
side. There you go.